{
    "subject": "resource/In_My_Chair",
    "predicate": "property/artist",
    "object": "resource/Status_Quo_(band)",
    "human_readable": "The artist of 'In My Chair' is Status Quo.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7694565653800964,
            "question": "Is Status Quo known for creating artwork?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7249619364738464,
            "question": "Who created the artwork 'In My Chair'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7144190073013306,
            "question": "Is 'In My Chair' a famous artwork?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6857823133468628,
            "question": "What other works are created by Status Quo besides 'In My Chair'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6474684476852417,
            "question": "What is the name of the artist behind the piece 'In My Chair'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6067719459533691,
            "question": "Which band is responsible for the artwork titled 'In My Chair'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5776145458221436,
            "question": "Can you describe the style of 'In My Chair'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5156697034835815,
            "question": "What is the subject matter depicted in 'In My Chair'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4299395978450775,
            "question": "Who might have commissioned 'In My Chair'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3059614598751068,
            "question": "Where can one find 'In My Chair' displayed?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The artist of 'In My Chair' is Status Quo.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3830_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who might have commissioned 'In My Chair'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3830_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the subject matter depicted in 'In My Chair'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3830_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you describe the style of 'In My Chair'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3830_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3830_114.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3830_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3830_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3830_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3830_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3830_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3830_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3830_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3830_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3830_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The documents mention that the song \"'In My Chair'\" is by the English rock band Status Quo, and it provides various details about the song, its release, chart performance, and more. This indicates that Status Quo is indeed the artist of the song \"In My Chair\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly indicate that \"In My Chair\" is a song by the English rock band Status Quo. Therefore, the statement \"The artist of 'In My Chair' is Status Quo\" is supported by the provided information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}